<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://example.org/brief-vita/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/brief-vita/</guid>
      
        <description>Brief Vitae    11/2022- &amp;nbsp &amp;nbsp now  Postdoc fellow  The Weizmann Institute of Science  At Yuval Oreg&#39;s group.   04/2018- 12/2022  PhD in nanophysics  Universidad Autónoma de Madrid  Title: Effects of the electrostatic environment on semiconductor/superconductor heterostructures; Advisors: Elsa Prada and Alfredo Levy Yeyati.  10/2021-05/2022: Research stay at The Weizmann Institute; Supervisor: Yuval Oreg.     12/2017- 03/2018  Research assistant  Universidad Autónoma de Madrid  Project: Visualizing, understanding and controlling Andreev Bound States down to atomic scale, funded by IFIMAC.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://example.org/conference-contributions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/conference-contributions/</guid>
      
        <description>Note: Some of the posters and talks were presented in conferences before their corresponding work was published. Hence, the files may contain incorrect or incomplete information.
  05/2022   CRC183  International conference organized by CRC183.   Poster contribution entitled &#34;Semiconductor-ferromagnet-superconductor planar heterostructures for 1D topological superconductivity&#34;, correspondingly.     03/2022   March meeting 2022  International conference organized by the American Physics Society at Chicago (USA).</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://example.org/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/publications/</guid>
      
        <description>Scientific publications   03/2022   Semiconductor-ferromagnet-superconductor planar heterostructures for 1D topological superconductivity  npj Quantum Materials 7, 81 (2022)  Authors: Samuel D. Escribano, Andrea Maiani, Martin Leijnse, Karsten Flensberg, Yuval Oreg, Alfredo Levy Yeyati, Elsa Prada and Rubén Seoane Souto. Arxiv link, Journal link, Bibtex reference.     01/2022   Fluxoid-induced pairing suppression and near-zero modes in quantum dots coupled to full-shell nanowires  Physical review B 105, 045418 (2022)  Authors: Samuel D.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>